Problem.create(board_size: 9, prompt: "Black to Capture", user_made: false, board: [[0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], [0, 1, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], [1, 0, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 0], [2, 2, 2, 2, 2, 1, 0, 1, 0], [0, 1, 0, 0, 2, 0, 0, 0, 0]], answer: [[0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], [0, 1, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], [1, 0, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 0], [2, 2, 2, 2, 2, 1, 0, 1, 0], [0, 1, 1, 0, 2, 0, 0, 0, 0]], move: "8-2", player: "Black", attempts: 0, solved: 0)

Problem.create(board_size: 9, prompt: "Black to Capture", user_made: false, board: [[0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], [1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0], [2, 2, 2, 2, 0, 1, 1, 0, 0], [0, 2, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0]], answer: [[0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], [1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0], [2, 2, 2, 2, 0, 1, 1, 0, 0], [0, 2, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0]], move: "8-3", player: "Black", attempts: 0, solved: 0)

Problem.create(board_size: 9, prompt: "Black to Live", user_made: false, board: [[0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], [0, 0, 2, 0, 0, 2, 0, 0, 0], [0, 0, 0, 2, 0, 0, 2, 2, 0], [0, 0, 2, 1, 1, 1, 0, 0, 0], [0, 0, 2, 1, 0, 0, 0, 2, 0], [0, 0, 2, 1, 0, 1, 0, 2, 0], [0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 1, 2, 0, 0]], answer: [[0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], [0, 0, 2, 0, 0, 2, 0, 0, 0], [0, 0, 0, 2, 0, 0, 2, 2, 0], [0, 0, 2, 1, 1, 1, 0, 0, 0], [0, 0, 2, 1, 0, 0, 1, 2, 0], [0, 0, 2, 1, 0, 1, 0, 2, 0], [0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 1, 2, 0, 0]], move: "6-6", player: "Black", attempts: 0, solved: 0)

Problem.create(board_size: 11, prompt: "Black to Capture", user_made: false, board: [[0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], [0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], [0, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], [1, 2, 2, 2, 2, 2, 1, 1, 1, 0, 0], [1, 2, 0, 1, 0, 2, 2, 2, 1, 1, 0], [0, 2, 2, 1, 1, 0, 2, 0, 2, 0, 0]], answer: [[0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], [0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], [0, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], [1, 2, 2, 2, 2, 2, 1, 1, 1, 0, 0], [1, 2, 0, 1, 1, 2, 2, 2, 1, 1, 0], [0, 2, 2, 1, 1, 0, 2, 0, 2, 0, 0]], move: "9-4", player: "Black", attempts: 0, solved: 0)

Problem.create(board_size: 12, prompt: "Black to Live", user_made: false, board: [[0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], [0, 0, 0, 0, 2, 0, 2, 0, 2, 0, 2, 0], [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 2, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], [0, 0, 0, 2, 2, 1, 1, 1, 1, 2, 2, 0], [0, 0, 0, 2, 1, 2, 2, 0, 1, 1, 2, 0], [0, 2, 0, 2, 1, 0, 2, 1, 0, 1, 2, 0], [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 2, 1, 0, 1, 2, 0]], answer: [[0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], [0, 0, 0, 0, 2, 0, 2, 0, 2, 0, 2, 0], [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 2, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], [0, 0, 0, 2, 2, 1, 1, 1, 1, 2, 2, 0], [0, 0, 0, 2, 1, 2, 2, 0, 1, 1, 2, 0], [0, 2, 0, 2, 1, 0, 2, 1, 0, 1, 2, 0], [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 2, 1, 0, 1, 2, 0]], move: "11-5", player: "Black", attempts: 0, solved: 0)

Problem.create(board_size: 10, prompt: "Black to Live", user_made: false, board: [[0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], [0, 1, 1, 1, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], [0, 2, 2, 2, 2, 2, 2, 0, 2, 0], [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], [0, 2, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0]], answer: [[0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], [1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], [0, 2, 2, 2, 2, 2, 2, 0, 2, 0], [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], [0, 2, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0]], move: "1-0", player: "Black", attempts: 0, solved: 0)

Problem.create(board_size: 14, prompt: "Black to Live", user_made: false, board: [[0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 2, 2, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], [0, 0, 0, 2, 0, 2, 2, 0, 0, 0, 2, 0, 0, 0], [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 2, 1, 0, 2, 2, 0, 0, 0, 0], [0, 2, 2, 1, 1, 1, 1, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 2, 2, 0, 1, 2, 2, 0, 0, 0], [0, 2, 2, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 0, 1, 0, 2, 0, 0], [0, 2, 1, 0, 2, 1, 0, 2, 0, 2, 2, 0, 0, 0], [0, 0, 2, 0, 2, 2, 0, 2, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], [0, 2, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0]], answer: [[0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 2, 2, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], [0, 0, 0, 2, 0, 2, 2, 0, 0, 0, 2, 0, 0, 0], [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 2, 1, 1, 2, 2, 0, 0, 0, 0], [0, 2, 2, 1, 1, 1, 1, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 2, 2, 0, 1, 2, 2, 0, 0, 0], [0, 2, 2, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 0, 1, 0, 2, 0, 0], [0, 2, 1, 0, 2, 1, 0, 2, 0, 2, 2, 0, 0, 0], [0, 0, 2, 0, 2, 2, 0, 2, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], [0, 2, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0]], move: "5-7", player: "Black", attempts: 0, solved: 0)

Problem.create(board_size: 12, prompt: "Black to Live", user_made: false, board: [[0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 1, 2, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], [0, 0, 2, 1, 0, 2, 0, 1, 1, 2, 0, 0], [0, 2, 0, 2, 1, 1, 1, 0, 2, 0, 2, 1], [0, 0, 0, 2, 2, 2, 2, 2, 0, 0, 0, 0], [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0]], answer: [[0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 1, 2, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], [0, 0, 2, 1, 1, 2, 0, 1, 1, 2, 0, 0], [0, 2, 0, 2, 1, 1, 1, 0, 2, 0, 2, 1], [0, 0, 0, 2, 2, 2, 2, 2, 0, 0, 0, 0], [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0]], move: "1-4", player: "Black", attempts: 0, solved: 0)

Problem.create(board_size: 9, prompt: "Black to Capture", user_made: false, board: [[0, 0, 0, 0, 2, 1, 0, 0, 0], [2, 2, 0, 2, 2, 1, 0, 0, 0], [0, 1, 2, 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 0], [0, 1, 1, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0]], answer: [[0, 0, 1, 0, 2, 1, 0, 0, 0], [2, 2, 0, 2, 2, 1, 0, 0, 0], [0, 1, 2, 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 0], [0, 1, 1, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0]], move: "0-2", player: "Black", attempts: 0, solved: 0)

Problem.create(board_size: 9, prompt: "Black to Capture", user_made: false, board: [[0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], [0, 1, 1, 1, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0], [0, 0, 1, 2, 2, 1, 1, 0, 0], [0, 2, 2, 2, 0, 2, 1, 0, 0], [0, 2, 0, 0, 0, 2, 1, 0, 0]], answer: [[0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], [0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0], [0, 1, 1, 1, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0], [0, 0, 1, 2, 2, 1, 1, 0, 0], [0, 2, 2, 2, 0, 2, 1, 0, 0], [0, 2, 0, 1, 0, 2, 1, 0, 0]], move: "8-3", player: "Black", attempts: 0, solved: 0)